(Hwang In Youp)
(Lee Hye Ri)
(Baek Sung Chul, Lee Yul Eum)
(Dream To You)
(All people, events, and backgrounds are fictional.) (This drama includes footage created using AI.)
(Children and animals were filmed under strict safety guidelines.)
What was that?
I should be asking you that.
Joo Yi Jae, are you crazy?
What's with you, Joo Yi Jae?
- Forget it. Stop following me. - Joo Yi Jae, you'll get soaked.
Okay. I won't walk with you, so just take the umbrella.
- Just take it... What? - No thanks.
You're really going to catch a cold.
It's none of your business if I catch a cold.
(Episode 5)
You're here?
Yes.
- "You're here?" - Sorry. Pretend it never happened.
It happened. How can we pretend it didn't?
I must've lost my mind while writing the kiss scene.
But you didn't write it.
I must've lost my mind trying to write it.
But actually, it's for the best.
We had to clear the air at some point anyway.
- Clear the air? About what? - I had to confirm how I felt.
Now that we're working together,
We can't let personal feelings get in the way.
So?
And did you find your answer?
The kiss scene needs to be written, but we shouldn't have done that.
Look at me and say it.
What? Look at what?
I said, look at me.
Spending every day together, I was confused about my feelings.
You know, you were always around, so I couldn't help but look at you,
And you got on my mind. That's why it happened.
Well, I'll make sure nothing like this happens again.
I'm sorry if I made you uncomfortable.
If that's your answer,
I don't want your apology.
We don't have to share our every raw emotion.
So from now on,
You deal with your feelings yourself.
Don't use me to figure them out.
Acting like this is so childish.
We're not 18 anymore.
Fine. I can do the whole "American style" thing.
The kiss scene needs to be written, but we shouldn't have done that.
"Clear the air?"
Then why did she kiss me?
Spending every day together,
- I was confused about my feelings. - So I was taken advantage of?
- Joo Yi Jae. - What?
Go home.
You think I won't leave when you tell me to?
Unbelievable, this guy. Who's being childish now?
I...
I'm leaving. This is so petty.
Hey. I was going to leave anyway. I'm leaving because I want to.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Su Bin told me to come get you.
He said it's dangerous at night and I should protect you.
That's ridiculous.
Right? He worries about the strangest things.
I'll protect you.
Are you insane?
- So, what are you going to do now? - What do you mean?
Aren't you coming home for good?
- Well... - "Well?" Then why are you here?
Where's Mom?
At the store.
You go on ahead.
- Why? - Just go in.
(Jaejae Noodles)
Hello.
It's amazing how none of that spills, right?
Gosh, look at that.
Who is she? She's so good. She's amazing.
Thank you.
She's so cool.
She's so nimble for her size.
Gosh, there she goes. Quick, catch it.
(What should I do?)
Mom.
I'm hungry.
I said I can eat carrots now.
You're not eating them because you want to.
Don't force yourself to eat things you don't like.
You, with your bad leg, climbed a mountain.
You, who's scared of water, fell into the ocean.
And you smiled while eating food you can't stand...
I just couldn't stand watching you like that.
It broke my heart.
(Savings Account: Joo Yi Jae)
If you don't like something, just say so.
Every day, just do whatever you want.
What would make me happy today? What would make me happy tomorrow?
Live like that from now on.
Don't think about me,
And don't think about Yeong Jae either.
- Mom. - Close your mouth. You'll spit.
A director's job is mostly done by sitting down somewhere, right?
Well, that's good then.
But, Yi Jae.
If you decided to work with him,
Shouldn't you tell him about that?
This is for your own good.
When you hide things,
It tends to make you act out in strange ways.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, are you okay? Ma'am.
(Woo General Hospital)
Fortunately, thanks to the quick response,
She's past the worst of it.
It was hypoglycaemic shock. Given her age,
We'd like to keep her for a few days to monitor her,
And I'd also recommend we run some tests to find the cause.
Okay, thank you, Doctor.
Hey.
You don't remember me?
(Specialist in Internal Medicine, Lee Mi Hyeon)
Lee Mi Hyeon?
Great. Great. Great expression.
Hey.
You looked good on TV,
But you've gotten even more handsome.
Hey, you look like a celebrity.
Have you been well?
I never thought I'd see you here.
Well, as you can see, this is how I'm doing.
I heard you came here.
I heard you stopped by my mother's restaurant for a meal?
- I did? - Didn't you go...
To A Lavish Feast with Yi Jae?
Right. Isn't it Jin Su's mom's restaurant,
- right? - Gosh.
Well...
Jin Su's mom is my mother-in-law.
- What? - Yes.
- So, you and Jin Su... - Yes.
- Okay. - Yes. What?
- Hey, can't you drive any faster? - Hurry up and run, will you?
- I think the makeup is a bit much. - Ready.
No matter how much I think about it...
- Is that what happened? - That's what happened.
- Mi Hyeon, hold on a second. - Okay, okay. I should get going.
Gosh, right. About Jong Seon...
She's definitely going to be stubborn and refuse to be admitted.
- Talk some sense into her. I'll go. - Okay. Take care.
Okay.
Jin Su and...
Mi Hyeon.
Next, we will present the Community Service Award...
For this year. Mok Gong Hui, congratulations.
Please welcome him with a big round of applause.
(Sim Yu Geon)
(Same Name, Different People)
(Theater Actor, Professor, Entrepreneur)
What is this?
Why isn't a profile showing up?
Hey, what are you doing? Everyone is watching us.
How much time is left on my contract?
Why do you ask? You're just going to renew it anyway.
Stop worrying about pointless things...
And focus on your meeting with Director Kim.
I don't know anything.
My contract gets renewed and my next project is chosen...
Without me even knowing.
It's so much easier for you. You just take what I give you. Gosh.
Sometimes I wish I were my own daughter.
Mom.
Even though I've never raised a child myself,
I've played the role of a mother many times.
If you just keep shoving food in before they can even digest,
The kid will throw up.
What do you mean by that?
Our next awardee is from Top Line Entertainment,
- CEO Ahn Soo Hee. Let's have... - We'll talk later.
A big round of applause.
Ahn Soo Hee has been making consistent donations,
And she will also be serving as the promotional ambassador...
- for our club. - Thank you.
There are many people here...
Who have given more generously than I have,
So I feel humbled to receive such an award.
The truth is, the reason I've been able to...
Consistently donate for nearly ten years...
Is because of my daughter, who is here with me today,
Ha Na.
Ha Na. Thank you.
Ha Na was filming today.
But she came to congratulate me on my award.
She just stopped by for a moment. Isn't she the sweetest?
In the future...
- Hello, I brought the laundry. - Okay.
Sir, I'm very sorry. There's a note saying the shirt...
- has some permanent stain on it. - It's fine.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(010-0895-3717)
Don't worry. Laundry service. Sorry. Excuse me.
Do you want to go out with me?
Why are you drinking in the middle of the day?
What does time matter?
When I get off work in the morning,
I day drink. Simple as that.
This brings back memories.
Hey, you should date someone new before you turn 30.
This is a really great opportunity for you.
Even if you don't find the one,
It'll be great publicity for your online store.
But still...
How could you ask me to be on the show?
Wait, are you still not over me?
We dated for 3 months, and we broke up 3 years ago.
That's really harsh.
Just do it for me once. Okay?
Come on, just appear on our show, "Love Chain," one time.
Who is it?
Hello.
This is Seo In Wook.
Sorry, who?
From the hotel. The shirt.
- The lipstick. - What?
The one you asked to date.
Do you want to go out with me?
Yes, baby.
Who was that?
- Hey, you should go. - What?
I said, go.
Choi Sa Rang, don't ever contact me again.
- Hello. - Yes.
Do you want to come here?
It's still early evening. Are you sure?
Of course.
So, should I keep you company? Or...
Should I get drunk with you?
Let's get drunk.
Something with a clean acidity and a distinct minerality.
The Dolce Vigna, this one.
The 2014 Vino, please. Thank you.
I'm not sure when it started for me, either.
The drinks just go down so smoothly.
Like a chicken just flutters and flies off.
- It happens. - That's what I thought.
That's right.
So this was to cast me for a dating show?
And you're the writer, Choi Sa Rang?
Yes. Well, our producer is the one...
Who was the producer of "Crazy Romance."
You know it, right? The one that was number one in buzz.
I've never heard of it.
But is that how you normally cast people?
No, normally we take applications or send DMs,
But you and I, what are we? Shall we call it fate?
So if I'm on the show, can I keep seeing you?
Of course. We'll probably be stuck together...
For two weeks until you're sick of me.
- And if I don't? - Then today will be the last time.
That would be a bit...
Of a shame, wouldn't it?
Why did you contact me?
Because I was curious.
About a woman who asks a guy to date her the moment they meet.
I was curious too.
About what you're like when you date, In Wook.
What is Woo Su Bin thinking? What time is it?
Hey, where are you?
Do you know how many times I've called you?
You're supposed to tell me...
When you're coming or where you're going.
- We agreed to share everything. - Sorry.
Jong Seon collapsed.
- I was rushing to the hospital. - What? Is she okay?
She tweaked her back a little,
But they said she should be admitted for more tests.
Okay.
I'm sorry, but...
I think you'll have to work by yourself today.
So you're not coming home tonight?
Well, I'm not sure yet.
Which hospital is it?
My father's hospital.
(Director Woo Cheol Gyu, Specialist of Cardiology)
Okay.
I'm going to stop by Jong Seon's house...
To grab some things she'll need.
You must not have been able to grab anything...
Since you left in such a hurry.
Yes. What's the room number?
Hey. Hey. Did you hear the news?
Director Woo is our Director's son, apparently.
- Really? The Director... - Good morning.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
(Nurses' Station)
What's going on?
It's probably because of your son, Director.
- What about my son? - He came to the hospital yesterday.
The rumour that Director Woo is your son spread like wildfire.
Come on, Director. When you have such an amazing son,
You could brag about him at least once, don't you think?
If it had been me,
I would've put him in the hospital's promotional videos.
I would've plastered his photos everywhere. Seriously.
Congratulations.
Well, he is impressive, though.
But still, it's not something to make such a big deal about.
Let's all just keep it quiet.
He...
Doesn't like a lot of fuss.
Yes, sir.
But...
Did they say why he came to the hospital?
Ms. Park Jong Seon.
My goodness.
- Gosh. You don't have to get up. - Gosh.
How are you feeling?
Yes, I'm all right.
Gosh, what brings a busy man like you all the way here, Director?
I heard about how much you helped my son.
- I had to come and thank you. - Gosh, it was nothing.
- Su Bin's the one who saved me. - Gosh, is that so?
By the way, where did Su Bin go?
Maybe he went to meet Yi Jae? She said she was coming.
Okay, yes.
I'll make sure you're well taken care of.
Gosh, thank you so much.
(Laboratory Medicine, IT Department and Nurses Department)
The doors are opening.
(Auto)
(Ventilation Fan)
(Power)
(Under Maintenance)
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
If you were so determined to sever our family ties,
You should've run so far away I couldn't reach you.
And you only made it...
Here?
It was to come back here.
So I could stop running away.
(Outpatient Clinic)
(Under Maintenance)
(Locker Room for Men)
- Gosh. - There's someone inside.
It's okay.
I'm right here, Woo Su Bin.
You don't have to come out.
Just...
Be aware that I'm here.
- Joo Yi Jae. About before... - I heard you met Mi Hyeon.
I haven't seen her since her wedding.
I even filmed their wedding video, you know.
- Really? - Yes.
Has it been about three years?
I should still have it somewhere.
I'll show it to you next time.
Sung Chan must've grown a lot. How old would he be now?
Is he starting school next year?
You said they got married three years ago.
They had the baby first.
If you see him, you'd know he's Kim Jin Su's son.
He's basically a Kim Jin Su Jr.
Gosh, right. I heard today...
That Jin Su quit his perfectly good job...
To write web novels.
What was his pen name again?
Jinsueocheonga.
What a grandiose pen name.
I heard that he doesn't earn a lot of money.
But I heard he does the housework and childcare...
Without complaining, so she just lets him be.
That's so like Jin Su.
Thanks, Joo Yi Jae.
(Oh Ha Na must be banned from acting in romantic comedies.)
(Her acting is so awkward.)
(Sang Yeon is carrying the show alone.)
(Is that a romance? It's a thriller.)
Stop reading the comments.
Do I really seem that bad to you?
"Bad?"
Your looks are overshadowing your acting.
You're a brilliant actress.
You've played a killer, a devil, a detective, even a judge.
You're great at playing everything from good guys to villains.
Then why am I so bad at romance roles?
Maybe... It's because you've never been in love?
By that logic, does that mean I've killed someone before?
Have you?
I'm kidding.
Ha Na.
When you're in love, it shows on your face.
Your eyes, your nose, your lips...
They're all directed at that person.
You can't hide it.
Please turn the car around.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
Will you order...
When the rest of your party gets here?
One serving of meat, please.
There's a two-serving minimum.
What brings you here?
I just felt like riding a motorcycle.
When do you get off work?
I have about an hour left.
I'll wait.
Okay.
Thank you.
It's pretty.
- Anyway, why don't you... - What?
Honestly...
- Who would turn down Oh Ha Na? - I would.
But I wonder if she's really never dated anyone.
Do you think it makes sense?
That's why so many people say she can't do romance, right?
Don't you think she'd be boring to date?
Hey, hey. Look at her eyes. Just look at them.
Hey, how can you say that after seeing the look in her eyes?
You can tell she's trouble for men. It's written all over her face.
Gosh. Exactly.
Who was that again? Ahn Soo Hee, right?
As soon as her husband's business failed, she divorced him, right?
After all that time she spent living the high life as his wife.
Gosh, she's a heartless jerk. How pathetic.
Well, they say a daughter inherits her mother's fate.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
- Like mother, like daughter. - Gosh, you scared me.
You're all being pretty loud.
- Boss, I quit. - Hey, what's going on?
- What's with him? - Hey, hey.
Why can't you say anything?
You were so quick to jump in and help...
When it came to other people.
So why do you always run away when it's your own problem?
- Why? - Gosh.
It's okay.
Those people are just...
The kind of people who can say those things,
And I'm the kind of person who's supposed to take it.
Get on.
Didn't you say you came for a motorcycle ride?
(010-0125-64...)
(010-0125-6458)
Thank you.
Why aren't you asking?
About how I found you.
It doesn't seem like the right time to ask that.
Well...
And I don't think you'd answer me anyway.
I looked you up online.
But for an actor, how come you don't have...
A single profile online?
Then where did you see me?
On social media.
When I searched your name,
A few web dramas...
And a picture of you serving at a BBQ place came up.
Those were all taken without your permission.
Should I sue them for you?
No.
But why did you look me up?
Look,
It's not fair.
We're friends,
But I'm the only one who knows so little about you.
You looked me up, didn't you?
If you search for Oh Ha Na, even my fortune comes up.
It says I'll make a ton of money.
But...
It also says that I'm fated to be lonely my whole life.
I didn't look you up.
Usually, when we're friends, I would ask in person.
I see.
My name is Sim Yu Geon,
And I'm 29.
And?
Our family members are...
Just my father and me.
And my hobby is...
Watching Hong Kong movies?
The reason I wanted to be an actor...
Was simply because...
Kaneshiro Takeshi was so cool.
- Get away. - Dad.
Why?
I, Sim Yu Geon,
Will become the Kaneshiro Takeshi of South Korea.
I've also made up my mind too...
- to wake you up with this net. - Oh, wait.
- You jerk. - It's cold. So cold.
My favourite movie is "Chungking Express."
My favourite line is...
"If love had an expiry date,"
"I'd wish for mine to be 10,000 years."
"I'd wish for mine..."
"to be 10,000 years."
That's my favourite line.
What? Break up? Hey, you can't break up with me.
It started with wanting to be Kaneshiro Takeshi.
Hey! If you want me...
- But at some point, - to die, I can pretend to die.
- it became about wanting to act. - Please see this.
(1st Audition of Alley Story)
Director. Director.
Yes, thank you for your work. You can go.
- Who chose him? - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Next, Han Dong Min, you may go in.
But it was hard to even get a chance to audition.
Hey, get in here. Come on. Let me hit you once.
Wait, hold on. Hey, what is this?
- Director Choi? - Yes.
This is real, right?
- Give it to me. - No, sir. It's dangerous...
Can't you see this, Director Choi? The look in their eyes has changed.
Let's shoot it like this.
- Ready, set, action. - Gosh.
Maybe...
I'll go my whole life without anyone ever knowing my name.
But even so,
If my dream had an expiry date,
I'd want it to be 10,000 years.
My father told me...
To just come home...
If I don't amount to anything in ten years.
But just like that, ten years have passed.
Without me amounting to anything.
What does "amounting to anything" even mean?
Who gets to set that standard?
Just go home.
You can go see your father and then come back, right?
- That's not what he meant... - I know.
But...
I just don't think his words sound all that cold.
It sounds like he's saying you can come home anytime.
Like the warm embrace of a parent.
I'm actually really jealous.
Jealous?
Let me...
Tell you something you won't find if you search for Oh Ha Na online.
- Is it fun? - I loved being on TV.
Let Mom make your hair pretty.
So pretty.
I have an all-night shoot. Please stay until tomorrow morning.
- Yes, of course. Have a good shoot. - Mom.
Should we watch some TV?
- Okay. - Who does our Ha Na take after?
You, Mom.
- Who's this pretty girl? - I was even happier there.
Oh Ha Na.
Without realising it was all fake.
- Right. Our Ha Na is the prettiest. - Ready, action.
- Ha Na's milk is one of a kind. - Please smile brighter.
- Ha Na's milk is one of a kind. - Make it prettier.
- Ha Na's milk is one of a kind. - We'll keep that. Let's go again.
Cut, cut. That's no good.
- Get Ha Na some water. - It's fine. You'll spoil her.
Ha Na.
Ha Na, what's wrong? Are you going to disappoint me?
Smile.
That's it. Ha Na is ready.
(Ha Na's High School)
Ha Na's High School.
Ha Na.
Good morning.
I heard you were filming late again last night.
You must be tired.
No, I'm fine.
Our Ha Na is amazing, isn't she? There's nothing she's lacking.
It makes me jealous.
But I eventually came to realise it.
- Thank you. - That my whole world is fake.
- Yes, teacher. - Yes.
When should we work on our project?
- Cut. - Tomorrow?
Ha Na, great work today. I'll see you at the next shoot.
Yes, great work today.
- Great work. - Great work.
Great work, everyone.
This is such a pain. When does this show end, Ha Na?
Sorry. It'll all be over next week.
I can't hold back this because it's so cringy.
- She was dying to be on camera... - Unbelievable.
Guys, I'm going to head out.
Bye.
Hey, take it easy.
News about her parents' divorce broke today.
Do I actually have something that even Oh Ha Na doesn't?
A happy family.
It's Oh Ha Na.
- Step back. - Did you know of their divorce?
We hear actress Ahn Soo Hee is starting...
An entertainment business with you.
What are your future plans?
- Step back! - Please answer...
- Please... - Is there any...
Please answer...
Director. You're starting a new project,
Aren't you?
- What is this? - Ha Na needs...
To shed her child image.
Please make some time for me. I'd like to come see you.
(Exclusive Artist Contract) Me?
I've been away from sets for a long time.
Right now, I'm busy supporting Ha Na.
How about I produce that project?
- To others, my world... - Yes.
- might seem pretty and sparkly. - Okay. I'll tell you later.
- Yes. - But me?
I want to walk off this set.
Like the ending of "The Truman Show."
It seems like you're already prepared to escape.
You said you know it's a set.
Now you just have to find that door.
You smiled.
That's the first time I've seen you smile like that.
(Don't get the wrong idea. This is for cleaning your ruined shirt.)
Leaving already?
I had fun.
But I'll block your number.
(Writer Choi Sa Rang)
Hey, did you finish reading that?
I slept with a woman a few days ago.
But I can't stop thinking about her.
- Stop or Go? - Stop.
Okay.
Go.
It should be more...
I don't know.
- You have to... - I know.
I got to go.
(Target Audience Proposal of Love Chain)
(HBS Entertainment Division, Writer Choi Sa Rang)
What brings you here?
- Is Writer Choi Sa Rang here? - Who's asking?
Seriously, I have no idea why Writer Choi didn't mention this.
No.
What do you mean, no? From head to toe,
You're exactly the contestant we've been looking for.
You were a producer in Hollywood for a while.
- Now, you're CEO of a film company. - Yes, that's correct.
You're intelligent and sexy.
- Okay, go. - Okay, go.
Wait, Producer Park, we've already finalised our cast.
I'm sorry, Mr. Seo In Wook, but all our spots are filled.
- Please leave. - Catfish.
You're the perfect catfish.
We'll have you make an entrance on day five.
Catfish, mosquito... Call me whatever you want.
My gosh. And a sense of humour too?
You're so perfect. I really like you.
I slept with this man.
- What? - I said, I slept with him.
So he can't be on the show, right?
Seo In Wook can't be on the show. Please leave now.
- Wait, wait. - Get out now.
How many times?
- What? - How many times did you sleep?
Once. A one-night stand.
- Are you in love with him? - Are you crazy?
- Are you in love with her? - No.
Okay, then. Let's cast him.
- Let's cast him. - Producer Park.
A one-night stand is better than an ex-boyfriend.
Don't you think?
- Go. - Go.
This is driving me crazy.
(Appearance Contract of HBS Dating Reality Show, "Love Chain")
- You think this situation is funny? - Yes.
Just say you won't do it. Please?
Please. I'll smooth things over with Producer Park.
Why should I?
Wait, an ex-boyfriend is okay, but I'm not?
- Don't tell me you like me. - Hey, Seo In Wook.
I'm the one who blocked you.
You're the one who came looking for me.
Then why did you block me?
You must have been disappointed to end it after just one time.
Unbelievable. I mean, that's...
How would you know that, Seo In Wook?
Did you poll all the women you've slept with?
- Agree? - No.
No.
I mean, am I supposed to sign here?
Are you sure you've read it carefully?
Absolutely no dating during filming.
Just in case any damages occur because of that,
There are clauses for contract termination...
And a full refund of your fee.
That obviously includes one-night stands,
Not just relationships.
Are you still okay with that?
You should probably control yourself.
Control myself?
Then what happens to you?
- What about me? - If you date a cast member?
Sorry, but I would never do that.
Especially not with you.
I have a rule that...
A 1-night stand ends as a 1-night stand.
Then, would you like to make a bet?
On whether or not there'll be a second time for us.
They say her one and only best friend died...
Because of Mu Gyeom.
And she'll tell Mu Gyeom about that?
Nan Yeong is in love with Mu Gyeom.
Why can't you understand how it feels to keep quiet...
Because she's afraid they'll fall apart?
She has to bear that pain.
No matter if his actions were for a greater cause,
It's a fact that he gave Nan Yeong an indelible wound.
What if Mu Gyeom leaves her over this?
Then that's all their love amounted to.
A love that can't even carry that weight...
Can it really last forever?
Then she'll never be able to tell him.
The fear of losing someone, more so than the promise of forever,
Can be a sign of even greater love.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Enjoy.
Gosh.
I still can't believe I'm seeing you two together.
- Look who's talking. - Gosh.
Seriously, I didn't believe it when they first started dating.
But then Mi Hyeon waited for him through his military service,
And he supported Mi Hyeon...
While she studied for her board exams.
Yi Jae, you should've beaten some sense into me back then.
- I did. - Gosh, right.
What?
- My darling, where did she hit you? - What are you doing?
Gosh, Joo Yi Jae, that girl's strong.
- She must've really laid into you. - Hey, stop. Come on.
Do you want me to beat you black and blue for old time's sake?
There you go with that "black and blue" talk again.
Haven't you seen these muscles?
- Where? What muscles? - Gosh.
I can't exactly show you. Honey, tell her.
- Tell her straight up. - Where are these so-called muscles?
- It's all muscle. - Where?
You want to go a round for old time's sake?
- You want to go? Bring it. - You want to try?
- Let's do it. - Should we?
(Mom, what about lunch tomorrow?)
Mom, what about lunch tomorrow?
(Sorry. I'm busy for the time being.)
You're here.
That's right, Gyeongseong Love Song. Gosh, that brings back memories.
Even right before the CSAT, Yi Jae, that's all you were writing.
Attention. This is an expert opinion of Jinsueocheonga.
This story seems to have a lot of holes.
Allow me to fill them in.
- Shut up. Don't be embarrassing. - Why? Let's hear him out.
-Are you serious? - Yes.
A protagonist who gives up revenge for love? No more. Never.
- Our Nan Yeong gives up on love. - But it's a romance.
A romance?
Listen up.
The year is 1930. The place, Gyeongseong.
On an empty street, frantic footsteps echo.
Every night,
I vowed to end that man's life with these hands.
But the heavens are cruel.
How could these same hands end up feeling your breath?
Nan Yeong.
I didn't know.
That the one who died by my hand...
- was your dear friend. - Cut the crap.
- Why are you pulling out a gun? - What? What's wrong with a gun?
That's so random.
Well, what? Are you supposed to get revenge with chopsticks?
Okay, aim the gun now.
As the two face each other tensely,
Cherry blossom petals scatter between them.
- It's winter. - Gosh, is it winter?
- Seriously. - I really can't stand the cold.
Can't you do this properly?
Okay, okay. All right, snow is fluttering down.
Ready, action.
My life already belonged to my country anyway.
But if I am to die by your hand,
I will gladly accept it.
For you too...
Were my country.
Not a day went by that I didn't think of you.
Because I loved you,
I will never be able to forget you.
Now that I've had my revenge,
Goodbye.
To have to kill the one you love with your own hands...
What a tragic fate.
Is that it?
So they don't achieve independence, and their love is unfulfilled?
- Runtime would be about 40 minutes. - Yes.
No wonder he doesn't make any money.
You're always going on about money in front of friends.
Gosh, this is so embarrassing, really.
This is good, though.
Yes.
- Eat it with the chicken. - Okay.
(Have fun with your friends. I'll call you later.)
(Always take care. See you soon. I love you, Mom.)
(Thank you, Su Bin. Mom loves you so much, my son.)
(Mom, how about lunch tomorrow?)
If you want to see the son you cherish so much,
You should get better as soon as possible.
Right?
For once, I'm finally a free man.
Honey, do you even know how I feel right now?
Do you even know the burden of being the head of the family?
Let's go, honey.
- Hey, we're heading out. - Just one more drink...
- See you around. Get home safe. - Bye.
- Bye. - All right, bye.
- Gosh. - What a bummer.
- I said I'm not drunk. - All right, all right.
My goodness.
Should we get going too?
Okay.
Going home?
Yes, where else?
- Let me walk you. - Oh, it's right around the corner.
I can go by myself.
Mom.
- Mom. - I'm sorry, Su Bin.
- I'm so sorry. - Let me see.
I shouldn't have let you see me like this...
Don't say that.
You're not the one who should be apologising. Gosh.
Don't. Don't.
- Don't. - Mom.
Don't.
Don't. Don't.
Su Bin.
My mom...
You shouldn't have laid a hand on her.
I'm not the one who hit her. You are.
Why did you have to come back and make this mess?
I told you I don't like blemishes.
Cut the crap before I kill you.
In case you've forgotten.
That woman is my wife.
She is not your mother.
Don't you ever...
Come near Mom and me.
Don't even look for us.
Su Bin.
You have a talent for ruining people.
And then you'll just run away again.
Like the coward you are.
We'll see.
Just you watch.
I'll be the permanent flaw in your life, Father.
Really?
Do you think you're a flaw only in my life?
How foolish.
You ran away to save your own skin, but she...
Nearly died trying to get you back.
(Woo General Hospital)
I heard that Yi Jae is awake.
Do you know why my daughter ended up like that?
It happened on her way to meet that son of yours.
Where is Woo Su Bin? Bring him here.
I'll do the same to him. I'll break his legs.
Say something. Say something.
- What would you do for her? - Ma'am, what are you doing?
What would you do for my Yi Jae? Let go of me.
I won't let this go. I won't just stand by.
- Are you all right? - Director, are you all right?
- Yes, I'm fine. - Yes.
Good grief.
Do you think you're a flaw only in my life?
Didn't you know?
That you're the one who ruined her life?
That you crippled her?
Woo Su Bin.
You are my regret.
You should go back to that day too,
And see how I feel.
What if Mu Gyeom leaves her over this?
Then she'll never be able to tell him.
(Dream To You)
I'm finally done.
Do you want to grab a drink to celebrate the first draft?
I'm not planning on staying here.
I'm getting out of here.
Gyeongseong Love Song?
The guy Ha Na was looking for... It was him all along?
- Hello? - It's me, Director Kang.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
How about you save the introductions for after location hunting?
- Right now? Why am I left out? - Let's just do it this way.
Who does some jerk from a no-name university...
- Get out. That's enough. - Hey.